## **TH Charlie KWONG**

## thkwong@friends.eduhk.hk

Charlie obtained his BA Degree with first-class honours from The Education University of Hong Kong, one of the research-intensive universities for Teacher Education and Training. Charlie serves as a pre-service teacher in elementary sector, curator and university research assistant for the research projects and knowledge transfer funded projects.

He has explored creative works in several areas including philosophy, Buddhism, spatial thinking, and digital culture. Past creative works have been featured and exhibited in the United Kingdom, Australia, South Korea, and Hong Kong.

## **EDUCATION**

2021 – 2022	The Chinese University of Hong Kong				
	Postgraduate Diploma in Education				
	<ul> <li>Teacher training qualification recognized by the Education</li> </ul>				
	Bureau of the Government of HKSAR				
2017 – 2021	The Education University of Hong Kong				
	Bachelor of Arts (Honours)				
	Honours Classification: First Class				
2019 – 2020	Fontys University of Applied Sciences, The Netherlands				
	International Student Exchange Scheme				
2018 – 2018	Masaryk University, Czech Republic				
	International Student Exchange Scheme				
2018 – 2019	The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, School of Design				
	Internal Student Exchange Scheme				

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2022	Postgraduate Research Assistant I (Seasonal)
	The Chinese University of Hong Kong
2021 - 2022	Research Assistant I (Part-time)
	The Education University of Hong Kong
2019 - 2021	Project Assistant - Specific Student Empowerment Work Scheme
	The Education University of Hong Kong
2018 - 2021	Blended Learning Associate
	Faculty of Liberal Arts and Social Sciences – EdUHK